[Music]
oh excuse me sir are you sitting in 26g
yes have I done something wrong
no no no we just wanted to ask if you
would mind switching seats so that a
mother and a child can sit together
and back there right yeah but you'd
actually be sitting here
which is an economy plus it's actually
an upgrade upgrade you say mm-hmm
Economy Plus yes sir Oh
don't mind if they do great great I'll
carry on carry on yourself Alex thank
you
[Music]
Economy Plus Oh for the discerning
passengers
we're not in Kansas anymore captain
speaking we should be leaving Topeka in
the next 10 minutes mister looks like
we're gonna have a smooth flight trust
me I know the captain
he's one good guy
[Music]
[Laughter]
of course he knows the captain he is the
captain
[Music]
oh-oh-oh
move over Colin Mochrie there's a new
face in the biz his name is Captain have
to be in Economy Plus to get it I guess
that's your foot room one inch at least
[Music]
Scottish bag O's mondo oh the dog is
mine continues Lord of the Rings cups of
the Rings tables
[Music]
and I thought I hadn't upgrade